Guide to the Cornell United Religious Work records, 1869-1972,
Cornell United Religious Work records
- Series I
  - Gershfield, Edward M, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 112)
  - Gezork, Herbert, 1959-61 (Box 16, Folder 113)
  - Gill, Theodore A, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 114)
  - Glaser, Rabbi Joseph B, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 115)
  - Glueck, Nelson, 1958 (Box 16, Folder 116)
  - Goldstein, Israel, 1958 (Box 16, Folder 117)
  - Gordon, Ernest, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 118)
  - Goss-Mayr, Hildegard, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 119)
  - Granskou, Clemens M, 1957 (Box 16, Folder 120)
  - Greeley, Dana McLean, 1961 (Box 16, Folder 121)
  - Green, Arthur, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 122)
  - Greenberg, Irving, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 123)
  - Gregory, Dick, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 124)
  - Hall, T William, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Hamill, Robert H, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Hamilton, William, 1961 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Harding, Vincent, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Hargraves, J Archie, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Harrington, Donald S, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Harrison, Beverly, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Harshbarger, Luther H, 1961 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Hartt, Julian N, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Haselden, Kyle, 1963-64 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Hatton, G Russell, 1974-75 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Haughton, Rosemary, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Hedley, George P, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Hehir, J Bryan, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Heidbrink, John, 1969 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Heiges, Donald R, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Helverson, Ralph, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Hendrick, John R (Pete), 1972 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Herberg, Will, 1955-65 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Hershey, Robert D, 1956 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Hertzberg, Arthur, 1966-76 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Heschel, Abraham J, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Heuss, John, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Hines, John E, 1963-68 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Hirshson, Louis, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Hofmann, Hans, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Hogan, Joseph L, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Holcomb, Harmon R, 1959-79 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Hoon, Paul W, 1958-63 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Hoover, Theressa, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Horn, Edward T, 1958-61 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Horton, Douglas, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - Howe, Reuel L, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - Howlett, Duncan, 1962 (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - Huchet-Bishop, Claire, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Hudnut, Will H Jr, 1956 (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - Hunt, Clark, 1961 (Box 17, Folder 37)
  - Iakovos, Archbishop, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 38)
  - Imes, William L, 1961 (Box 17, Folder 39)
  - Jack, Homer A, 1959-67 (Box 17, Folder 40)
  - Jaquith, L Paul, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 41)
  - Jenkins, Daniel, 1960-62 (Box 17, Folder 42)
  - Johanson, Brian O, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 43)
  - Johnson, Philip A, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 44)
  - Jones, Lawrence, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 45)
  - Jones, Richard, 1970-71 (Box 17, Folder 46)
  - Jospe, Alfred, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 47)
  - Judd, Walter, 1961 (Box 17, Folder 48)
  - Kahn, Benjamin M, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 49)
  - Karp, Abraham, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 50)
  - Kavanagh, Aidan, OSB, 1969-71 (Box 17, Folder 51)
  - Kelleher, Stephen J, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 52)
  - Kennedy, Gerald, 1957-60 (Box 17, Folder 53)
  - Ketchem, Charles B, 1961-64 (Box 17, Folder 54)
  - Kinsolving, Arthur Lee, 1957-63 (Box 17, Folder 55)
  - Kirkland, Bryant, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 56)
  - Knight, John, 1962-63 (Box 17, Folder 57)
  - Knox, John, 1963 (Box 17, Folder 58)
  - Konvitz, Milton R, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 59)
  - Kring, Walter D, 1957-58 (Box 17, Folder 60)
  - Kruener, Harry H, 1955 (Box 17, Folder 61)
  - Kuhn, Margaret, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 62)
  - Lall, Abner, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 63)
  - Lander, Yechiael, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 64)
  - Laverty, A Marshall, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 65)
  - Latourette, Kenneth S, 1961 (Box 17, Folder 66)
  - Lawson, O'Kelly, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 67)
  - Lefvre, Perry, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 68)
  - Lehmann, Paul, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 69)
  - Lincoln, Eric, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 70)
  - Lindsay, Samuel, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 71)
  - Lipman, Eugene J, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 72)
  - Littell, Franklin, 1964-73 (Box 17, Folder 73)
  - Locke, Hubert G, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 74)
  - Long, J Bruce, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 75)
  - Lowry, Howard, 1958 (Box 17, Folder 76)
  - Luccock, Emory W, 1957-58 (Box 17, Folder 77)
  - Luccock, Robert, 1960-62 (Box 17, Folder 78)
  - MacColl, James R III, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 79)
  - Macquarrie, John, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 80)
  - Masden, Truman G, 1969-70 (Box 17, Folder 81)
  - Macguire, John David, 1969-70 (Box 17, Folder 82)
  - Mainwaring, Donald J, 1968-69 (Box 17, Folder 83)
  - Maitland, David, 1960-62 (Box 17, Folder 84)
  - Martin, John R, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 85)
  - Marty, Martin, 1964-74 (Box 17, Folder 86)
  - Mathews, James K, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 87)
  - Mathews, Joseph W, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 88)
  - Maurer, Tom B, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 89)
  - Maxwell, Kenneth L, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 90)
  - Mazobere, Crispin C G, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 91)
  - McBrien, Richard, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 92)
  - McCall, John R, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 93)
  - McCandless, Hugh, 1962-64 (Box 17, Folder 94)
  - McCombe, John H Jr, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 95)
  - McCord, James I, 1965-66 (Box 17, Folder 96)
  - McCracken, Robert J, 1962 (Box 17, Folder 97)
  - McCullough, Charles, 1968-69 (Box 17, Folder 98)
  - McKay, Arthur R, 1957-65 (Box 17, Folder 99)
  - McKersie, Robert B, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 100)
  - Medina, Harold R, 1957-58 (Box 17, Folder 101)
  - Mein, Peter Simon, 1971-72 (Box 17, Folder 102)
  - Mellin, John O, 1962 (Box 17, Folder 103)
  - Mendelson, Jack, 1969 (Box 17, Folder 104)
  - Mesaros, Frank, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 105)
  - Michalson, Carl, 1954-56 (Box 17, Folder 106)
  - Miller, Alexander, 1955 (Box 17, Folder 107)
  - Mollegen, Albert T, 1956-63 (Box 17, Folder 108)
  - Monick, Eugene, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 109)
  - Moody, Howard, 1960-77 (Box 17, Folder 110)
  - Morikawa, Jitsuo, 1966-67 (Box 17, Folder 111)
  - Morton, James P, 1973-75 (Box 17, Folder 112)
  - Mosley, J Brooke, 1968-71 (Box 17, Folder 113)
  - Muehl, William, 1964-66 (Box 17, Folder 114)
  - Napier, B Davie, 1963-73 (Box 17, Folder 115)
  - Neill, Stephen C, 1961 (Box 17, Folder 116)
  - Nelson, C Ellis, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 117)
  - Nelson, Douglas E, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 118)
  - Nelson, John Oliver, 1961-63 (Box 17, Folder 119)
  - Nettle Brent, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 120)
  - Newland, Mary Reed, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 121)
  - Nicole, Roger, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 122)
  - Niebuhr, Reinhold, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 123)
  - Niemoeller, Martin, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 124)
  - Niles, Daniel T, 1959-66 (Box 17, Folder 125)
  - Noble, Charles C, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 126)
  - Novak, Michael, 1969 (Box 17, Folder 127)
  - Ockenga, Harold J, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 128)
  - Ogden, Schubert M, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 129)
  - Ortmayer, Roger, 1968-70 (Box 17, Folder 130)
  - Outler, Albert C, 1960-64 (Box 17, Folder 131)
  - Oxnam, G Bromley, 1957-58 (Box 17, Folder 132)
  - Ozick, Cynthia, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 133)
  - Padovano, Anthony T, 1971-72 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Parsonage, Robert Rue, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Parsons, E Spencer, 1963-71 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Parvey, Constance, 1972-77 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Peel, Robert, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Pemberton, Prentice L, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Pennington, Chester A, 1959-62 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Perry, Samuel L, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Petuchowski, Jakob J, 1973-74 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Pilchik, Ely E, 1957 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Pinnock, Clark H, 1973-74 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Phillips, JB, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Pintauro, Joseph, 1971-72 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Price, Charles P, 1967-68 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Rahmeier, Paul W, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Rahtjen, Bruce D, 1974-75 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Raines, Richard C, 1957 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Rankin, Robert, 1972-73 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Rauf, M Abdul, 1975-76 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Read, David H C, 1957-60 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Reagan, Ewell, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Redhead, John A, 1960-81 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Rees, Ethan, 1959-65 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Repp, Ray, 1971-73 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Reppert, Nelson, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Rexine, John E, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Rich, Wendell O, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Richardson, Herbert W, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Riemer, Jack, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Rivers, Clarence Jos, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Robinson, Donald A, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - Rogers, William W, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - Rohlfs, Ruth, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - Ross, Elisabeth Kubler, 1972-74 (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - Rubenstein, Richard L, 1966-75 (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - Ruether, Rosemary, 1967-73 (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - Rutenber, Culbert, 1962 (Box 18, Folder 37)
  - Sagan, Carl E, 1977-79 (Box 18, Folder 38)
  - Sanders, J Alton, 1966-67 (Box 18, Folder 39)
  - Saunders, Wilbour, 1957-59 (Box 18, Folder 40)
  - Saxby, Harold, 1972-74 (Box 18, Folder 41)
  - Schomer, Howard, 1961-64 (Box 18, Folder 42)
  - Scott, Robert A, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 43)
  - Schmemann, Alexander, 1960-66 (Box 18, Folder 44)
  - Schwartzchild, Steven, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 45)
  - Shaull, Richard, 1966-67 (Box 18, Folder 46)
  - Shepard, J Barrie, 1969 (Box 18, Folder 47)
  - Shinn, Roger, 1959-64 (Box 18, Folder 48)
  - Shoemaker, Samuel M, 1958-60 (Box 18, Folder 49)
  - Sibley, Mrs. Harper, 1959-63 (Box 18, Folder 50)
  - Siirala, Aarne, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 51)
  - Silberman, Lou H, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 52)
  - Silver, Abba Hillel, 1957 (Box 18, Folder 53)
  - Sittler, Joseph Jr, 1957-72 (Box 18, Folder 54)
  - Sizoo, Joseph R, 1957-60 (Box 18, Folder 55)
  - Skogland, John, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 56)
  - Sleeth, Ronald E, 1958-63 (Box 18, Folder 57)
  - Smith, Eugene L, 1966-68 (Box 18, Folder 58)
  - Smith, Harry E, 1970-75 (Box 18, Folder 59)
  - Smith, Robert, 1960-62 (Box 18, Folder 60)
  - Snook, Lee E, 1969-71 (Box 18, Folder 61)
  - Sockman, Ralph W, 1957-62 (Box 18, Folder 62)
  - Speakman, Fred, 1959-60 (Box 18, Folder 63)
  - Steimle, Edmund, 1957-73 (Box 18, Folder 64)
  - Stern, Merold, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 65)
  - Storey, William G, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 66)
  - Struchen, Jeanette, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 67)
  - Summerlin, Ed, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 68)
  - Tang, Emery, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 69)
  - Taylor, Theophilus, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 70)
  - Thomas, James S, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 71)
  - Thurman, Howard, 1957-59 (Box 18, Folder 72)
  - Tillich, Paul, 1960-62 (Box 18, Folder 73)
  - Toner, Richard, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 74)
  - Torgersen, Gordon M, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 75)
  - Totonji, Ahmad, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 76)
  - Trakatellis, Demetrius, 1969-70 (Box 18, Folder 77)
  - Trueblood, Elton, 1965-72 (Box 18, Folder 78)
  - Trungpa, Chogyam, 1971-72 (Box 18, Folder 79)
  - Tucker, Bobby, 1967-77 (Box 18, Folder 80)
  - Tulis, Edward A, 1969 (Box 18, Folder 81)
  - Udy, James Stuart, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 82)
  - Underwood, Richard A, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 83)
  - Unsworth, Richard, 1970-71 (Box 18, Folder 84)
  - Vahanian, Gabriel, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 85)
  - Verghese, T Paul, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 86)
  - Verghese Lectures, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 87)
  - Visser, 't Hooft WA, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 88)
  - Volatis, Constantine, E, 1964-69 (Box 18, Folder 89)
  - Vorspan, Albert, 1973-78 (Box 18, Folder 90)
  - Walsh, Chad, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 91)
  - Warner, C Terry, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 92)
  - Webber, George W, 1969 (Box 18, Folder 93)
  - Wedel, (Mrs.) Theodore O (Cynthia), 1966-72 (Box 18, Folder 94)
  - Wedel, Theodore O, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 95)
  - Weind, Teresita, 1977-78 (Box 18, Folder 96)
  - Wellborn, Charles, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 97)
  - West, Robert N, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 98)
  - Whitney, Yenwith K, 1972-73 (Box 18, Folder 99)
  - Wicke, Lloyd C, 1960-61 (Box 18, Folder 100)
  - Wiesel, Elie, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 101)
  - Wilkinson, Howard, 1963 (Box 18, Folder 102)
  - Willenbrock, F Karl, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 103)
  - Williams, Colin W, 1966-72 (Box 18, Folder 104)
  - Williams, Daniel D, 1956 (Box 18, Folder 105)
  - Wood, Virgil A, 1969 (Box 18, Folder 106)
  - Wright, John J, 1965-66 (Box 18, Folder 107)
  - Yeakel, Joseph, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 108)
  - Young, Franklin, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 109)
  - Young, G Douglas, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 110)
  - Student Board, 1963-64 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - CURW Student Board, 1962-63 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Student Board Minutes, Memos, Agendas, 1961-62 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Student Board, 1960-61 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Student Board, 1959-60 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Ex comm and student board, 1958-59 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Student board, 1958-59 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Student Board, 1957-58 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Student board, 1956-57 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Student board, 1955-56 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Student board, 1954-55 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Student board minutes, 1953-54 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Student board, 1952-53 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Student board minutes and agendas, 1951-52 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Student board, 1950-51 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Student board and exec comm minutes, 1949-50 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Student board, 1949-50 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Student board minutes, 1944-45 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Student Board, 1941-49 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Student Board, 1948-49 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Student Board, 1948 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Student Board, 1944 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Minutes of the student board, 1942-44 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Student Board minutes, 1940-41 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Minutes of student board, 1939-40 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Student board minutes, 1938-39 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Student joint board, 1937-38 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Minutes of student joint board, 1936-37 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Student joint board minutes and records, 1934-36 (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Memos, 1963-65 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Memos, 1960-63 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Memos, 1960-61 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - CURW memos, 1955-73 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1957-63 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1960-61 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Memos from Office of Dean, 1966-77 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Action taken by exec comm of board of trustees, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - CURW assessments and props, 1963-74 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - CURW Minutes of board meetings, 1951-64 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - CURW staff minutes and attached papers, 1968-69 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - CURW views definitions, 1957-61 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Inter-religious cooperation, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - CURW reports to the board, 1959-69 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Council of federated min., 1960-63 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - CURW staff, 1967-68 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Board of control, 1963-79 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - University chaplains, 1958-71 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - CURW Counseling Services, 1967-81 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - CURW General information, 1951-72 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Diagram of CURW Structure, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Calendar Scheduling general info, 1950-76 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Calendar, 1960-61 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Calendar, 1959-60 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Advisory committee, 1953 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Personnel and job description, 1965-80 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Persons considered for director of CURW, 1954 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Personnel Women's cabinet, 1930s/40s (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - CURW resumes, 1969-74 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - Gordis, Robert, 1957-67 (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Re Jeanne Brown, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Canham, Erwin D, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - Maxfield, Otis, 1967 (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - CRESP Board of directors, 1974-80 (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - Civitas, 1966-74 (Box 20, Folder 35)
  - Religious organizations, 1960-61 (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - Rural Church Institute, 1960-61 (Box 20, Folder 37)
  - Association for humanistic psychology, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 38)
  - Info and councils on alcoholism, 1974-79 (Box 20, Folder 39)
  - Minutes of board of directors Hilo, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 40)
  - EARS, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 41)
  - 50th Anniversary celebration CURW, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 42)
  - CURW retreat, 1957 (Box 20, Folder 43)
  - Courses offered CURW, 1964 (Box 20, Folder 44)
  - Mott Student committee, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Mott Colloquy Materials, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Mott Centennial, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Mott, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Life of Mott, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Mott Colloquy 1, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Dr Morris Mitchell, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Professor Steven Muller, Director, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Dr Richard Schaull, 1965-66 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - The Rev Alexander Schmemann, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Dr Paul Abrecht, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Dona Marina Bandeiro, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Dorothy Day, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Dr. WH Ferry, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Dr WA Visser 'tHooft, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Mr. John Heidbrink, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - L'Abbe Francois Houtart, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Father Mooney, 1965-66 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Hacker, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Professor J Edward Dirks, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Professor Milton Konvitz, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Dr James Perkins, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Sir Kenneth Grubb, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - DL Mumby, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Dr. Alice Mary Hilton, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Dr. Wm. Birenbaum, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Professor Robert Cohen, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Professor Johannes Hoekendijk, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - Paul Goodman, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - John R Mott Colloquy 2, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - Social Responsibility, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - Harmon Holcomb, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - Mott Evaluation, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - People interested in material on outcome of colloquy, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 34)
  - Education Area, 1958-59 (Box 21, Folder 35)
  - Fraternity contacts, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 36)
  - Graduate Supper Club, 1951-60 (Box 21, Folder 37)
  - Graduate Area Advisory board, 1957-58 (Box 21, Folder 38)
  - Religious Vocations group, 1956-57 (Box 21, Folder 39)
  - Religious vocations group, 1957-58 (Box 21, Folder 40)
  - Religious vocations group, 1958-59 (Box 21, Folder 41)
  - Religious Vocations, 1960-61 (Box 21, Folder 42)
  - Institutional Deputations, 1959 (Box 21, Folder 43)
  - Deputations - Panel of Americans, 1956 (Box 21, Folder 44)
  - High school deputations, 1956-57 (Box 21, Folder 45)
  - Rural church deputations, 1956-60 (Box 21, Folder 46)
  - Suggestions - compiled by Rick Cohen, 1958-59 (Box 21, Folder 47)
  - Pre-college orientation, 1959-60 (Box 21, Folder 48)
  - Deputations general correspondence, 1960-61 (Box 21, Folder 49)
  - Pre-college orientation teams, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 50)
  - Deputations - Addison/Alton/Auburn, 1956-59 (Box 21, Folder 51)
  - Deputations - Binghamton/Cato-Meridan, 1957-61 (Box 21, Folder 52)
  - Deputations - Cortland, Dryden, Dundee, Geneva, Greenwood, 1957-58 (Box 21, Folder 53)
  - Deputations - Groton, Hannibal, Haverling, Hornell, 1956-59 (Box 21, Folder 54)
  - Deputations - Horseheads, 1960 (Box 21, Folder 55)
  - Deputations - Interlaken, Middlesex, New Berlin, Newark Valley, 1959-60 (Box 21, Folder 56)
  - Deputation - Norwich, Odessa, Ovid, Owego, Penn Yan, Romulus, 1956-59 (Box 21, Folder 57)
  - Deputations - Seneca Falls, Savona, Sherburne, Spencer, Tioga, 1958-60 (Box 21, Folder 58)
  - Deputations - Trumansburg, Union, Endicott, Union Springs, Van Etten, 1956-61 (Box 21, Folder 59)
  - Deputation - Waterloo, Watkins Glen, etc, 1958-61 (Box 21, Folder 60)
  - Deputations - Students/Teams, 1959 (Box 21, Folder 61)
  - Deputation - General notes, 1960 (Box 21, Folder 62)
  - Deputation - Evaluations, 1960 (Box 21, Folder 63)
  - Pre-college Literature, 1960 (Box 21, Folder 64)
  - Freshman Club, 1953-54 (Box 21, Folder 65)
  - Student Appraisal Teaching Courses, 1960 (Box 21, Folder 66)
  - Student board lists, 1940-70 (Box 21, Folder 67)
  - Policy Boards for Major Projects, 1946 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - International Service Central America, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - International Service Brazil, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Honduras Project, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Cuando Project, 1970 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Nigerian Project, 1959-62 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Latin America Projects:general, 1967-70 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Latin American Projects, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Greek Project, 1956 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - East Harlem, 1965-66 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - East Harlem Project, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Cornell East Harlem Project Report and Evaluation, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Spring Vacation, 1960 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - National Service Suburban Poverty Project Yonkers-White Plains, 1969 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Cornell Power Project, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Iranian Project Summer, 1956 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Iranian Project, 1956 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Roland Delattre and Robert Day correspondence, 1957 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Migrant Labor proposed project, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Project Understanding, 1962-63 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Nova Scotia Project, 1964 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - International Area, 1955-57 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - International Weekend, 1961 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Community Service Area, 1956-57 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Community Service, 1957-60 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Discrimination, 1961 (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - Civil Rights Newsletter, 1963-64 (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - March on Washington, 1964 (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - Sit-in-sixties, 1960s (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - UN and Washington Trips, 1951 (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - Voter Registration Project, 1964 (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - Life Safety Devices on Campus Bridges, 1952-53 (Box 22, Folder 32)
  - For Such a Time as This, 1958 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Freshman General Area, 1951 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Interest Inventory Questionnaire, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Frosh Area, 1959-60 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Freshman Area, 1958-59 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Freshman Area, 1957-58 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Freshman Area Mimer Material, 1956 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Freshman Area Committee, 1955-56 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Freshman Area - Preliminary Thinking Spring, 1955 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Freshman Area Board Minutes, 1959 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - University Freshman Committee, 1958-59 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Freshman Open House, 1959 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Freshman Open House, 1958 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Freshman Open House Publicity, 1957 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Freshman Open House, 1956 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Foreign Student Orientation, 1960 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Foreign Student Orientation, 1950 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Orientation conference for new foreign students, 1956 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Freshman Camps, 1960 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - University Orientation, 1960-61 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Working Folder Camp Insurance, 1965-71 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Freshman Camp, 1957-58 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Frosh Replies Discussion Groups, 1956 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Freshman Planning board, 1956-57 (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Freshman Day, 1956 (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Freshman Camp, 1956-57 (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Sourcebook, 1955 (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - Sourcebook Sky Lake, 1955 (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - Sourcebook Arrowhead, 1955 (Box 23, Folder 29)
  - Fresh Notes, 1955 (Box 23, Folder 30)
  - Committee on the freshman year, 1955 (Box 23, Folder 31)
  - CURW freshman orientation, 1955 (Box 23, Folder 32)
  - Freshman camp staff and faculty, 1955 (Box 23, Folder 33)
  - Freshman Camp planning weekend, 1955 (Box 23, Folder 34)
  - Freshman camp counselor, 1955 (Box 23, Folder 35)
  - Freshman camp general, 1955 (Box 23, Folder 36)